What's up, guys? Today, I'm going to
show you how to create a commercial for
your e-commerce brand using Flick AI.
So, here I have an image of my product,
uh, which is an energy drink. So, I'm
going to drop it into the Flick chat,
and I'm going to say, "Make me a
commercial for my
product."
Enter.
So,
now the agent is going to think about
what kind of commercial to make, and
it's going to ask me a few questions
about the style and type of commercial I
want to do. And right now, it's
analyzing the image, and it's going to
propose some questions for me based off
this analysis. We can see here on the
left, we have a file system where the
image has been saved, and you can also
upload documents, videos, any other type
of media for your brand as well, and the
agent can analyze this and include it in
its context for the commercial. So, now
it's asking me some questions. How long
should the commercial be? I'm going to
say,
"15 seconds for now."
What's the vibe? I'm going to say, "High
energy."
Any talent or characters in it? I'm
going to say,
"Yes, let's show people."
So, now the agent is going to load the
Produce Video skill, and it's going to
create a plan for the commercial.
So, right now the agent is thinking
through the plan for the commercial
based on the context and the
answers that I gave it here.
And it's going to start writing a .md
file, which is a type of file for the
agent to read and stay on track for the
project, similar to how Cloud Code, uh,
also uses .md files for its plans.
So, now we see it creating the plan file
here.
And it's going to pop up in the file
system in a moment.
All right. So, here is the plan
document. So,
right now
it's talking a little bit about the
approach, the assets that it has
available, the assets that it's going to
create, the creative direction,
film grammar,
video prep path,
everything that it needs to
fully create and produce a full
commercial. I'm going to say, "This
looks good.
Let's do it."
And if there's anything on here that we
want to edit, like say
I want to do it 720p instead of 1080p, I
can just type directly in this chat
or I can just type directly in this
document and change anything I want.
So, now I'm approving the plan.
Now, the agent is loading the character
and location skills and it's going to
draft the creative direction document.
So, now we can see here it created the
files folders for
our location assets, our character
assets, our audio,
anything that it needs to generate. So,
everything's structured here
in the
file system.
So, now it's writing the creative
direction document.
Okay. So, the creative direction
document is done.
So, I'm going to review it here.
Let's do it. And then it asked me a few
questions.
Which tagline should we do? Stay lucid,
locked in, clarity over everything, or
don't blur.
I'm going to say
locked in tagline
and male athlete.
You choose the sport.
So, you can see here it shows a
MMA fighter for the athlete.
Now, it's going to create the characters
and the location.
So, before it creates the characters and
the locations, it's going to create a
visual style document that will help the
agent structure the prompts for the
images and the videos.
So, here we see the visual style.
Great.
Now, it's generating the images of the
characters and locations. We can see
here that it's using GPT image 2, 1K
resolution, 9 by 16 aspect ratio. And as
we can see, the agent prompted all this
on its own using the context from the
project and knowing how it's going to
create the commercial. So, you don't
have to prompt, you don't have to write
all this stuff down. You don't have to
know the structure for the prompts. The
agent knows all this and writes it for
you.
And if you want to fine-tune it, you can
always go in, copy the prompt, edit it,
anything you want.
So, now the images have started to come
in.
Here's the first one.
Location image of a gym
with a
boxing bag.
And here is our athlete.
This all looks great.
So now the agent is analyzing the
images, making sure they came out
correctly.
I'm going to say, yes, these work.
Let's
go.
So now the agent is going to create a
spatial model
for this location, so that the location
is mapped 360 degrees for the video
generation.
All right, so the spatial model is
complete. Now the agent is moving on to
the director shot list. So we can see it
right here.
Now the shot list is locked and
uh the agent is going to create the
video.
And it's going to use all these images
as assets
for the video.
And
we'll see
how it does.
So as we can see here,
the agent is creating the video.
This is the prompt that it used to
prompt C dance.
And these are the images that it used.
Okay, so it looks like our final video
came in, so let's watch it.
Cool. So
we can see it used our
asset here
and it created a full length commercial.
So now if I want,
I can put the video into
our editor
and edit it however I want.
So yeah, that's how you create a
commercial for your e-commerce brand
using Flick.